Finding Aid for the John Phillip Hyatt Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files
    - Archaeology--North Semitic Epigraphy (Box 34, File 1-3)
    - Archaeology--Magazine Clippings (Box 34, File 4)
    - Archaeology--Newspaper Clippings (Box 34, File 5-6)
    - Archaeology--Notes (Box 34, File 7-11)
    - Archaeology--Palestine (Box 34, File 12)
    - Archaeology--Photographs (Box 34, File 13-15)
    - Archaeology--Wright, G. Ernest (Box 34, File 16)
    - Archaeology--Miscellaneous (Box 34, File 17)
    - Baptism (Box 34, File 18-19)
    - Baptist Polity and History (Box 34, File 20)
    - Alexander Campbell (Box 34, File 21)
  - Subject Files
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Bibliographies (Box 35, File 1)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Hodayot (Box 35, File 2)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Magazines, etc. (Box 35, File 3-5)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Magazine Clippings (Box 35, File 6)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Newspaper Clippings (Box 35, File 7)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Scholarly Papers and Arts. (Box 35, File 8-12)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Translations (Box 35, File 13-15)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--University of Wisconsin Radio Series (Box 35, File 16)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Notes (Box 35, File 17-20)
  - Subject Files
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Miscellaneous (Box 36, File 1)
    - History and the Historian (Box 36, File 2)
    - Indian Religion (Box 36, File 3)
    - Islam (Box 36, File 4)
    - Jerusalem (Box 36, File 5)
    - Judaism (Box 36, File 6-7)
    - Languages--Aramaic (Box 36, File 8-9)
    - Languages--Babylonian-Assyrian (Box 36, File 10-17)
    - Languages--Hebrew (Box 36, File 18-20)
    - Languages--Latin (Box 36, File 21)
    - Languages--Linguistics (Box 36, File 22)
  - Subject Files
    - Languages--Sumerian (Box 37, File 1)
    - Languages--Syriac (Box 37, File 2)
    - Languages--Ugaritic (Box 37, File 3)
    - Marxism (Box 37, File 4)
    - New Testament--Apocalyptic (Box 37, File 5)
    - New Testament--Gospel of John (Box 37, File 6)
    - New Testament--Jesus (Box 37, File 7-8)
    - New Testament--Miscellaneous (Box 37, File 9)
    - Old Testament--Ark and Ephod (Box 37, File 10)
    - Old Testament--Conquest (Box 37, File 11)
    - Old Testament--David (Box 37, File 12)
    - Old Testament--Dress (Box 37, File 13)
    - Old Testament--Love in Old Testament (Box 37, File 14)
    - Old Testament--Man in Old Testament (Box 37, File 15)
    - Old Testament--Messianism (Box 37, File 16)
    - Old Testament--Mosaic Faith (Box 37, File 17)
    - Old Testament--Myth in Old Testament (Box 37, File 18)
    - Old Testament--Pentateuch (Box 37, File 19-20)
    - Old Testament--Poetry (Box 37, File 21)
    - Old Testament--Prophecy (Box 37, File 22-24)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament--Salvation in Old Testament (Box 38, File 1)
    - Old Testament--Solomon (Box 38, File 2)
    - Old Testament--Text and Canon (Box 38, File 3-5)
    - Old Testament--Theology (Box 38, File 6-10)
    - Old Testament--Torah in Old Testament (Box 38, File 11)
    - Old Testament--Typology (Box 38, File 12)
    - Old Testament--Wisdom Literature (Box 38, File 13)
    - Old Testament--Yahweh (Box 38, File 14-16)
    - Old Testament Books--Genesis (Box 38, File 17-18)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament Books--Exodus--Notes (Box 39, File 1-2)
    - Old Testament Books--Exodus--Articles (Box 39, File 3-10)
    - Old Testament Books--Deuteronomy (Box 39, File 11)
    - Old Testament Books--Job (Box 39, File 12-15)
    - Old Testament Books--Psalms (Box 39, File 16-18)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament Books--Proverbs (Box 40, File 1)
    - Old Testament Books--Ecclesiastes (Box 40, File 2)
    - Old Testament Books--Isaiah (Box 40, File 3-4)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah (Box 40, File 5-9)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah 39:3 (Box 40, File 10)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah--Repentance (Box 40, File 11)
    - Old Testament Books--Amos (Box 40, File 12)
    - Old Testament Books--Jonah (Box 40, File 13-14)
    - Old Testament Books--Micah (Box 40, File 15)
    - Old Testament Books--Habakkuk (Box 40, File 16)
    - Old Testament Books--Sirach (Box 40, File 17)
    - Old Testament Books--Wisdom of Solomon (Box 40, File 18)
    - Pastoral Counseling (Box 40, File 19)
    - Social Justice (Box 40, File 20)
    - Theology--Contemporary (Box 40, File 21)
    - Theology--Pannenberg--Bibliographies, etc (Box 40, File 22)
    - Theology--Pannenberg--Papers (Box 40, File 23-25)
    - Theology--Scriptural Authority (Box 40, File 26)
    - Vietnam (Box 40, File 27-28)
  - Personal
    - Oddities (Religious and Other) (Box 41, File 1)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 41, File 2)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Baylor University (Box 41, File 3)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Branscomb Distinguished Professor (Box 41, File 4)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--United Christian Missionary Society (Box 41, File 5)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Christian Theological Seminary (Box 41, File 6)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Texas Christian University (Box 41, File 7)
    - Charitable Giving (Box 41, File 8)
    - Education Materials--University of Marburg (Box 41, File 9)
    - Education Materials--Yale Divinity School (Box 41, File 10)
    - Family--Elizabeth Bard Hyatt (Box 41, File 11)
    - Family--Lee Hyatt (Box 41, File 12)
    - Family--Robert Lee Hyatt--Cancelled Checks (Box 41, File 13)
    - Family--Robert Lee Hyatt--Legal Papers (Box 41, File 14)
    - Health Matters (Box 41, File 15)
    - High School Reunion (Box 41, File 16)
    - Legal Papers--Bradley Lumber Co. (Box 41, File 17)
    - Legal Papers--Insurance and Miscellaneous (Box 41, File 18)
    - Legal Papers--Union Bank and Trust (Box 41, File 19)
    - Legal Papers--War Manpower Commission (Box 41, File 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 41, File 21)
    - Photographs (Box 41, File 22)
    - Resumes, Vitae, etc. (Box 41, File 23)
    - Travel--Europe and Middle East (1931-32)--Diary (Box 41, File 24-25)
    - Travel--Geneva Trip (1965)--Receipts (Box 41, File 26)
    - Travel--Geneva Trip (1965)--Miscellaneous (Box 41, File 27)
    - Miscellaneous Personal (Box 41, File 28)
    - Loose Calendar/Appointment Books--1951, 1952, 1954 (Box 41, File 28)
  - Personal and Writings by Others
    - Loose Calendar/Appointment Books—1955, 1956, 1956¬57, 1957-58, 1958-59, 1959-60, 1961, 1961-62, 1962¬63, 1963-64, 1964-65, 1965-66, 19666-67, 1967-68, 1968-69, 1969-70, 1970-71, 1971-72 (Box 42)
- Writings by Others
  - R. L. Hyatt—Short Stories (Box 42, File 1-10)